<resources>

    <string name="Mon_app_name">CashOut</string>
    <string name="app_name">CashOut</string>
    <string name="nointernet">Please check your internet connection and try again</string>
    <string name="title">CashOut</string>
    <string name="startapp_id">207741404</string>
    <string name="myDroidAdmobapp_id">ca-app-pub-5836526993277102~6434973492</string>
    <string name="myAdmobapp_id">ca-app-pub-5836526993277102~6434973492</string>
    <string name="googleAdmobapp_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>
    <string name="myAdmobInter_unitid">ca-app-pub-4156752697881993/6186955975</string>
    <string name="myAdmobInterReward_unitid">ca-app-pub-4156752697881993/6123818708</string>
    <string name="myAdmobReward_unitid">ca-app-pub-4156752697881993/4626888296</string>

    <string name="monAppID">ca-app-pub-6799639509419386~6349245996</string>
    <string name="monInter_unitid">ca-app-pub-6799639509419386~6349245996</string>
    <string name="monInterReward_unitid">ca-app-pub-6799639509419386~6349245996</string>
    <string name="monBannerid"> ca-app-pub-6799639509419386~6349245996</string>

    <string name="loading">loading</string>
    <string name="logout">log out</string>
    <!--    <string name="default_web_client_id">752345349547-3lgva9m044uq40q0nreu85piids2aqn1.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>-->
    <!-- res/values/strings.xml -->

    <string name="about_us_content"><![CDATA[

   Cashout is a Professional Financial Platform where you Earn income daily by performing certain task provided by Us. We in-turn payout to our legitimate users seventy (70) percent of their earnings while we keep thirty (30) percent of the total earnings.

    Here we will provide you only interesting content, which you will like very much. We\\\'re dedicated to providing you the best of Financial help that with eradicate financial deficit, with a focus on dependability and Online Earning.

    We\'re working to turn our passion for Financial availability into a booming Online Earning. We hope you enjoy our Financial provisions as much as we enjoy offering them to you.

    We will keep serving you more important information on our Application for all of you. Please give your support by adhering to our policies, terms, and conditions.

    Thanks For Using Our App!

    Have a nice day!
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agreement"><![CDATA[

Welcome to CashOut earning platform! Before you start using our earning platform, please take a moment to read and understand our user agreement. By accessing or using CashOut, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions outlined below. \n

1. Acceptance of Terms

By using CashOut, you agree to comply with and be bound by these terms of use. If you do not agree with any part of these terms, please do not use our platform.\n

2. Modification of Services

CashOut reserves the right to modify, suspend, or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the service or any service to which it connects, with or without notice and without liability to users. We may make changes to the platform to enhance user experience or address technical issues.

3. Actions for Sustenance

In the interest of sustaining CashOut as a viable earning platform, we reserve the right to take certain actions that may or may not affect users\' earnings. These actions could include, but are not limited to, adjusting earning rates, introducing new features, or implementing measures to maintain the overall health of the platform. \n

4. User Responsibilities

Users are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of their account information, including passwords. You agree to notify CashOut immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security.\n

5. Eligibility

To use CashOut, you must be at least 18 years old and capable of forming a binding contract. By using our platform, you confirm that you meet these eligibility requirements. \n

6. Earnings and Payments

CashOut provides users with the opportunity to earn rewards or cash through various activities. Earnings are subject to the terms and conditions specified within the platform. Users acknowledge that their earnings may be affected by actions taken by CashOut for the sustenance of the platform, as outlined in Section 3.\n

7. Termination of Accounts

CashOut reserves the right to terminate user accounts at our discretion, without prior notice, if we believe that a user has violated these terms or engaged in fraudulent or inappropriate activities. \n

8. Privacy and Data Security

CashOut is committed to protecting user privacy. Please review our Privacy Policy to understand how we collect, use, and safeguard your information. \n

9. Governing Law

This user agreement is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Nigeria. Any disputes arising from or in connection with this agreement shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in [Your Jurisdiction].\n

10. Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns about this user agreement, please contact us at sun2meg@gmail.com.

By using CashOut, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agreed to these terms and conditions. We may update this agreement periodically, and it is your responsibility to review it regularly for any changes. Continued use of CashOut after modifications constitutes acceptance of the updated terms.\n

Thank you for choosing CashOut! Happy earning!\n

 *Disclaimer*

We are not responsible for any content, code or any other imprecision. We do not provide warranties or guarantees. In no event shall we be liable for any special, direct, indirect, consequential, or incidental damages or any damages whatsoever, whether in an action of contract, negligence or other tort, arising out of or in connection with the use of the Service or the contents of the Service. We reserve the right to make additions, deletions, or modifications to the contents on the Service at any time without prior notice.

Our Service and its contents are provided "as is" and "as available" without any warranty or representations of any kind, whether express or implied. We are a distributor and not a publisher of the content supplied by third parties; as such, our exercises no editorial control over such content and makes no warranty or representation as to the accuracy, reliability or currency of any information, content, service or merchandise provided through or accessible via our Service. Without limiting the foregoing, We specifically disclaim all warranties and representations in any content transmitted on or in connection with our Service or on sites that may appear as links on our Service, or in the products provided as a part of, or otherwise in connection with, our Service, including without limitation any warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non- infringement of third party rights. No oral advice or written information given by us or any of its affiliates, employees, officers, directors, agents, or the like will create a warranty. Price and availability information is subject to change without notice. Without limiting the foregoing, we do not warrant that our Service will be uninterrupted, uncorrupted, timely, information given by us or any of its affiliates, employees, officers, directors, agents, or the like will create a warranty. Price and availability information is subject to change without notice. Without limiting the foregoing, we do not warrant that our Service will be uninterrupted, uncorrupted, timely, or error-free.

 \n
 *Contact Us*

Don\'t hesitate to contact us if you have any questions. \n

• Via Email:
megacoreapps@gmail.com

Via WhatsApp Phone Number: +2347049374664 \n

• Via Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/sunny.s.umoh \n

]]></string>

</resources>
